<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hi, I&#39;m Erik</title>
    <link>www.erikvanek.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hi, I&#39;m Erik</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 22:43:35 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="www.erikvanek.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>School times &amp; misc</title>
      <link>www.erikvanek.com/commin-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 22:43:35 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.erikvanek.com/commin-up/</guid>
      <description>Random parts of my life not fitting anywhere else but still worth mentioning.
School times Before being competent to work in software industry, I&amp;rsquo;ve graduated from Computer graphics and digital image processing at Faculty of Informatics, Masaryk University in Brno. It went well, especially that part with playing with Kinect. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while though :)
For my masters, I decided to attend Information studies with emphasis on service design at KISK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software development</title>
      <link>www.erikvanek.com/development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 22:17:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.erikvanek.com/development/</guid>
      <description>What is my favourite platform you may as. Open web I&amp;rsquo;d reply. Web is an amazing medium that is free to use to everyone. No vendor lock-in, no proprietary tools. On the other hand, it suffers from the fact that it was constructred as a network for exchange of documents. It was just simple hypertext back then. Times have changed. Today&amp;rsquo;s internet users expect smooth, interactive yet reliable tools. It&amp;rsquo;s challenging to deliver those, but pleasing when done properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hi. I&#39;m Erik Vaněk</title>
      <link>www.erikvanek.com/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 20:03:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.erikvanek.com/me/</guid>
      <description>I like to do stuff. Grow greens for example or develop on the web.
Who am I? That&amp;rsquo;s a good one. Glad you ask. Trying to find out lately. At least 20 years.
Overgrown brat? Hopefully not.
Professionally software developer for several years. Wannabe designer, hobby cook. Sometimes constructive hater. Loyal person. You need to earn this loyalty though. I love my family, friends, sports and good sleep. Food indeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fresh greens all year long</title>
      <link>www.erikvanek.com/aero/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 20:02:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.erikvanek.com/aero/</guid>
      <description>This is one of my sideprojects I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on mainly during 2016 and 2017. It stems from two connected facts. First is that one of my biggest hobbies is food. Second is that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to prepare tasty meals without fine ingredients. I do not mean fancy. Rather fresh and full of taste, preferably seasonal and local.
This is even more obvious outside of green season say between mid October til the beginning of May.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>