1. Scrape two websites: registry of social services in your region and health services nationwide. Extract all types of services.
2. Reduce the scraped categories to 20-30 broader categories based on similarity.
Create an interactive single-page website for a card-sorting game. Users start by seeing all categories and can intuitively combine them.
Add a feature that allows users to name each cluster of categories they create during the card-sorting process.
Implement a feature to send the results of the categorization to the email address 'kemboi@ezekiel.yup' for analysis.
Add visual cues to encourage 6-8 categories. Use mild pastel colors and a counter to nudge users. Be playful in copywriting and use gratification patterns.
Add a feature to delete categories while keeping services in the list. Use different colors for each category. Implement 'Roboto' font and improve visual rhythm.
Provide clearer guidance to users. Consider using bullet points or emojis. Replace the generic headline with a more engaging, funky name.
When sending the email, include three open-ended questions about categorization choices, missing categories, and interest in overall results.
Ensure the website is mobile-friendly to accommodate users on various devices and screen sizes.
Ensure each new category has a unique name (e.g., "group1", "group2"). Prompt users for their name and include it in the email signature with results.